Guide to the School of Forestry and Environmental Studies, Yale University, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1985-2010; Accession 2014-A-075
  - Records of Dean Gus Speth
    - Transition to Sustainability, 2000 November - August 2003 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Transparency International, 2000 February-March (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Transportation and the Environment Proposal, 36586 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Trinidad - University of the West Indies (File 1 of 2), 2003 February-November (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Trinidad - University of the West Indies (File 2 of 2), 2006 May - 2007 January (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Trinidad and Tobago, 2003 February-April (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Tropical Biology Association, 2004 April-August (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Tropical Forests and the Human Spirit (Book), 2000 December - 2001 June (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Trust for Public Land, The, 2001 May-February (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Trust Funds and Confirming Council/World Bank, 2001 October (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Tufts - Comment for Jacket, 2000 May - 2003 December (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Twenty-First Century Forum - Conference 2000, 2000 March - 2000 July (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Tyler Prize, 1985 October - 2002 June (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - United Nations Conference on Environment and Development (UNCED), Undated, circa 2001 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - UNDP - Global Environment Facility, 2002 January (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - UNDP - Yale, 2000 March - 2002 April (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - UNDP/UNOPS - Yale University for the Public Private Partnerships Programme, 2000 January (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - UNDP - World Energy Assessment, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - UNEP - Sasakawa Environment Prize, 2000 April-August (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - UN Global Conference on Finance, 2002 February (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - UNITAR - Student Conference 3/27/2000, 2000 March (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - UNDP - United Nations - File 1 of 4, 1991 August - 1993 November (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - UNDP - United Nations - File 2 of 4, 1993 December - 1994 March (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - UNDP - United Nations - File 3 of 4, 1994 August - 1995 March (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - UNDP - United Nations - File 4 of 4, 1996 July - 1999 September (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - United Nations Staff College/FES Joint Program, 2000 August (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - United Nations Association of U.S. of America, 1999 August - 2004 February (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - United Nations Commission on Sustainable Development, 2003 April (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - United Nations - Campaign for U.N. Reform (CUNR), 2002 February (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - United Nations Development Program (UNDP), 2001 January - 2003 April (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - United Nations Institute for Training and Research (UNITAR), 2000 November - 2001 February (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - United Nations Publications, 2000 November - 2002 January (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - United Nations Population Fund (UNFPA), 2002 August (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - United Nations University, 2000 February - 2001 June (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - United Nations Environment Program/Intergovernmental Panel on Global Environmental Change, 2004 December - 2007 June (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - United Nations Environment Program (UNEP), 2002 December (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - United Nations Foundation, 2003 February-September (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - USAID/Guinea, 2000 June (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - US-ASIA Environmental Partnership, Undated (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - U.S.-China Center, 2000 November - 2001 January (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Underhill Foundation, 1998 December (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - United States Department of Agriculture, 1998 July - 1999 June (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - United States Department of State, 2001 January-June (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - United States Environmental Protection Agency (US EPA), 1996 June - 2000 October (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - United Way, 2000 August (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - Universities Council on Water Resources, 1990 July - 1999 October (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - University for Peace, 2001 March - 2002 January (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - University for Peace, Advisory Meeting on the Academic Program of the, 2001 March (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - University of Connecticut Sea Grant College, 2001 August - 2006 September (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - University of Minnesota, 2000 March - 2004 June (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - University of Singapore - Environmental Management Program, 2002 June - 2004 June (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - University of Vermont, October 1992 - July 2000 (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - University of Wisconsin System - Agriculture and Natural Resources (1989), 2000 July-August (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - Upstate Forever, 2002 May (Box 13, Folder 73)
    - Urban Agriculture Network, 2001 May (Box 13, Folder 74)
    - United States Agency for International Development (USAID), 2003 February-April (Box 13, Folder 75)
    - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA), 2001 December (Box 13, Folder 76)
    - United States Department of Agriculture Forest Service (USDA Forest Service), 2002 March (Box 13, Folder 77)
    - United States Fish and Wildlife Service - National Conservation Training Center, 2001 October (Box 13, Folder 78)
    - United States Green Building Council, Undated (Box 13, Folder 79)
    - U.S. News and World Report, 2001 October-December (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - V. Kann Rasmussen Foundation, March 2003 - January 2005 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Vietnam National University, Undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Volvo Prize, 1999 December - 2000 November (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Wagner Forest Management Ltd., 2001 August-September (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Washington Environmental Council, 36557 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Washington Post, 2000 January- 2002 June (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - WBSCO Report, 37165 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - WEHAB (Water, Energy, Health, Agriculture, and Biodiversity), 37408 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - West Hill Foundation for Nature, 37226 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - West Virginia University - Davis College of Agriculture, Forestry and Consumer Sciences, 38139 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Weyerhauser Company, 1998 - 2003 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Who's Who In the World, 2002 - 2005 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Wilderness Society, 1995 February - 2001 November (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Wildlife Conservation Society, The, 2000 February - 2001 November (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Willrich-Strohbehn Dinner, 36647 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Wilderness Society, 37956 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Wishcamper Group, 2004 January-February (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Woods Hole Research Center - Board of Directors Meeting, September 29, 2006, 38961 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Woodrow Wilson Center, 2000 April - 2001 October (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Woods Hole Marine Sciences, 2004 October (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - World Affairs Council, 2000 August (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - World Bank, 2001 December (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - World Bank (World Resources), 2000 February- 2001 March (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - World Business Council for Sustainable Development (WBCSD), 2000 May - 2003 March (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - World Economic Forum, 2002 September (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - World Environment Center, 1989 April - 2001 May (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - World Federalist Association of New England (WFANE), 2002 July (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - World Food Programme, 2002 January (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - World Forest Congress, 1997 March-April (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - World Institute for Development Economics Research (WIDER), 2000 December (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - World Parks Congress, 2003 April (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - World Wildlife Fund, 1989 March - 2001 September (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - World Summit on Sustainable Development, 2001 December - 2002 August (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Johannesburg - Sept 2002, 2002 August (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - World Trade Organization (WTO), 2002 February (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Worldwatch Institute, 2000 June - 2002 December (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - World Wildlife Fund - U.S., 2000 January - 2004 September (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - World Wildlife Fund - J. Paul Getty Conservation Prize, 2002 September - 2003 September (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - WBZ Science Center Berlin, 1999 September - 2001 December (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - Yale Club of New Haven Scholars, 2000 April (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - Zayed International Prize for the Environment, 2001 January- 2003 December (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - Administration (Yale University), 2003 February (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - Affirmative Action (Yale University), 1995 July - 1999 May (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - Alliance for Lifelong Learning (Yale University), 2002 January (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - Anthropology (Yale University), 2002 November (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - Architecture (Yale University), 1989 September-December (Box 14, Folder 73)
    - Architecture School - Joint Degree Program, 2000 February (Box 14, Folder 74)
    - Association of Yale Alumni, 1990 September - 2003 June (Box 14, Folder 75)
    - Center for Business and Environment at Yale (CBEY), 2007 August (Box 14, Folder 77)
    - Center for Environmental Risk, Estimation and Management, 1993 July (Box 14, Folder 78)
    - Center for Human Ecology, Environment and Infectious Disease, 1991 October-November (Box 14, Folder 79)
    - Class of 1964, 2003 April-September (Box 14, Folder 80)
    - Class of 1936, 2000 October (Box 14, Folder 81)
    - Conservation Easement, 2001 August-September (Box 14, Folder 82)
    - Consultative Group for International Activities at Yale, 2000 September- 2002 August (Box 14, Folder 83)
    - Deputy Provost - Pierre Hohenberg, 1995 September - 1999 April (Box 14, Folder 84)
    - Director of Information/Library Systems Search Committee, 1997 March (Box 14, Folder 85)
    - Divinity School, 1983 September - 1997 February (Box 14, Folder 86)
    - Environmental Programs at Yale, 2002 April - 2008 September (Box 14, Folder 87)
    - Environmental Sciences Facility, 1994 April - 2001 March (Box 14, Folder 88)
    - Facilities, 1993 March - 2001 December (Box 14, Folder 89)
    - FES at Yale, 2000 April (Box 14, Folder 90)
    - Finance Administration/Financial Systems Steering Committee, 1996 May - 2005 February (Box 14, Folder 91)
    - Foot Program, 2000 November (Box 14, Folder 92)
    - Fuel Cell Technology, 37165 (Box 14, Folder 93)
    - GESO (Graduate Employees and Student Organization, 1999 September-November (Box 14, Folder 94)
    - Graduate School, 2000 April - 2005 November (Box 14, Folder 95)
    - Graduate-Professional Student Senate at Yale, 1997 July - 2001 August (Box 14, Folder 96)
    - Graduation 2004, 38108 (Box 14, Folder 97)
    - Greening Of... Yale Initiative, 2000 September-August (Box 14, Folder 98)
    - History Department, 1993 June - 2002 April (Box 14, Folder 99)
    - Honorary Degrees for Commencement, 1999 December - 2002 November (Box 14, Folder 100)
    - Human Rights and Development Law Journal, 37257 (Box 14, Folder 101)
    - Human Resources Dep't., Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Indirect Costs - Yale University, 35551 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Institute for Biospheric Studies/Center for Earth Observation, 1999 November - 2004 February (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Institute for Biospheric Studies, 2002 September- 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Institutional Policy Committee, 36617 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - International Interdisciplinary Professorships, 2003 May-November (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - International Security Studies, 2000 May - 2001 September (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Institution for Social and Policy Studies (ISPS), 1993 January - 2001 April (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Lamar Center, 2000 September (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Law School, 1994 November - 2007 January (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Library, Sterling Memorial, 1987 May - 1998 March (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Marsh Botanical Garden, 1998 March - 2002 September (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Medical School, 1987 April - 1990 June (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Minority Students, 1998 May - 2006 January (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - New Haven Affairs, Office Of, 1999 January - 1999 October (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Nursing, School of, 1984 October - 2002 September (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Office of Budget and Planning, 2000 October - 2002 December (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Pierson College, 1999 December - 2000 November (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - President's Office, 1998 May - 2006 April (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Program in Management and Environment (PM and E), 2000 June (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Provost's Office - 1990-1994, 1990 December - 1994 October (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Provost's Office - 1995-1998, 1995 January - 1998 October (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Provost's Office - 1996-2006, 1999 January - 2006 January (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Rudd Center, 2008 February (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Standing Advisory and Appointments Committee (SAAC) - FES, 2009 October (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - SAAC Members, 2001 February - 2005 August (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Sangha River Network (SRN), 1999 November - 2000 December (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Sangha River Network (2), 2000 March (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Science Hill Branch Office, 2000 March - 2001 October (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Science Hill Facilities Planning Committee (File 1 of 2), 1994 January - 1995 February (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Science Hill Facilities Planning Committee (File 2 of 2), 1995 December - 2000 November (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Security at Yale, 2001 January (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Secretary's Office, 1990 January - 2001 March (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Sino Forest/Yale SDLP, 2002 July (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Society of American Foresters, 2003 February - 2009 December (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Society of Environmental Journalists (SEJ), 2000 March-June (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Sociology Department, 2002 September (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Steering Committee, 1999 November (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Strike March 2003, 2003 February-March (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Studies in the Environment - File 1 of 2, 1993 October - 1994 December (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Studies in the Environment - File 2 of 2, 1995 February - 2000 July (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Teaching of Ecology at Yale, 1996 October (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Tercentennial, 1999 February - 2001 December (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Trinational Sangha River Region, 1997 March - 1999 September (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - School of Management, 1998 February - 2002 September (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - UBC Committee, 1999 November - 2001 July (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - University Advisory Council of Yale-New Haven Teachers, 2002 November - 2002 December (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - University Committees, 1995 May - 2002 April (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - University Tribunal, 1983 October - 2000 October (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Veterans' Program (State of Connecticut), 1994 September - 1999 March (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - World Fellows' Program, 1996 September - 2003 December (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Yale Center for International and Area Studies - File 1 of 6, January 1989 - September 1993 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Yale Center for International and Area Studies - File 2 of 6, 1994 August - 1996 January (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Yale Center for International and Area Studies - File 3 of 6, 1996 July - 1999 August (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Yale Center for International and Area Studies - File 4 of 6, 2000 February - 2000 November (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Yale Center for International and Area Studies - File 5 of 6, 2000 April - 2000 September (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Yale Center for International and Area Studies - File 6 of 6, 2000 September - 2004 March (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - YCIAS Professorships, 2002 October-December (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Yale Alumni Association, 1999 December - 2001 August (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine, 1997 March - 2002 October (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Yale Club of New Haven, 2000 April - 2003 May (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Yale College, 1987 August - 2002 October (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Yale's Fourth Century, 2001 November (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Yale College Teaching, 1998 November - 2000 April (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Yale College - Joint Bachelor's/Master's Program, 2000 July - 2001 April (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Yale Daily News, 1999 December - 2000 January (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Yale Institute for Biospheric Studies (YIBS) - File 1 of 3, 1996 February - 1998 February (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Yale Institute for Biospheric Studies (YIBS) - File 2 of 3, 1998 March - 2002 December (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Yale Institute for Biospheric Studies (YIBS) - File 3 of 3, November 2000 - April 2004 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - YIBS External Advisory Board - File 1 of 2, 1993 September - 1999 May (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - YIBS External Advisory Board - File 2 of 2, 1994 March - 1997 February (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - YIBS - "Population and Habitat", 1997 May (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - YIBS - G. Evelyn Hutchinson Prize (Anu Awasthi), 1996 May (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Yale's Environmental Sustainability Program (YES Program), 2000 May (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Yale Herald, 2000 November (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Yale International Relations Association, 1999 October (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Yale Medals, 2001 July (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Yale-New Haven Teachers' Institute - File 2 of 2, 2002 December (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Yale-New Haven Teachers' Institute - File 1 of 2, 1994 July - 2002 December (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Yale Political Monthly, 1994 March-April (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Yale/UNDP - Public-Private Partnership Program, 1997 February (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Yale Printing Services, 1999 December (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Yale Science and Engineering Association, Inc. (File 1 of 2), 1992 November - 2002 October (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Yale Science and Engineering Association, Inc. (File 2 of 2), 1988 October - 1992 October (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Yale Scientific Magazine, Undated (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Yale Student Environmental Coalition (YSEC), 2000 March - 2001 December (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Yale University Press, 1989 January - 2000 July (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - The Yale, 2001 April - 2002 March (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Yale Tours, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Yale Volunteer Services, 1987 May - 1990 August (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Yale World Fellows Program, 2002 March (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - YCEO (Yale Center for Earth Observation), 2003 February (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - YCIAS (Yale Center for International and Area Studies), 2002 January-February (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Year 2000 Project, 1998 July (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Appointments- 2004 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Jan 15, 2003, 2003 January (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Feb 12, 2003, 2003 February (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Special Meeting - Mar 4, 2003, 2003 March (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Mar 26, 2003, 2003 March (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Apr 16, 2003, 2003 April (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - May 14, 2003, 2003 May (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Sep 17, 2003, 2003 September (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Oct 15, 2003, 2003 October (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Nov 12, 2003, 2003 November (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Dec 17, 2003, 2003 December (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Jan 21, 2004, 2004 January (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Feb 18, 2004, 2004 February (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Minutes - Mar 25, 2004, 2004 March (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Apr 21, 2004, 2004 April (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - May 19, 2004, 2004 May (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Jun 29, 2004, 2004 June (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Sep 15, 2004, 2004 September (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Oct 19, 2004, 2004 October (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Dec 16, 2004, 2004 December (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Feb 4, 2005, 2005 February (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Mar 4, 2005, 2005 March (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Apr 22, 2005, 2005 April (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - May 20, 2005, 2005 May (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Sep 16, 2005, 2005 September (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting -Nov 11, 2005, 2005 November (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Dec 9, 2005, 2005 December (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Feb 24, 2006, 2006 February (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Dec 15, 2006, 2006 December (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting Agenda - Jan 26, 2007, 2007 January (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Mar 2, 2007, 2007 March (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Apr 13, 2007, 2007 April (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Sep 14, 2007, 2007 September (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Oct 26, 2007, 2007 October (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Dec 14, 2007, 2007 Dev (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Jan 25, 2008, 2008 January (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Feb 22, 2008, 2008 February (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Special Meeting - Mar 5, 2008, 2008 March (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Apr 18, 2008, 2008 April (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - May 16, 2008, 2008 May (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Sep 12, 200 Sep, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Nov 14, 2008, 2008 November (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - February 6, 2009, 2009 February (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - March 6, 2009, 2009 March (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - May 15, 2009, 2009 May (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Oct 2, 2009, 2009 October (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Meeting - Nov 13, 2009, 2009 November 13 (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Board of Permanent Officers - Dec 11, 2009, 2009 December (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - BPO Vote - Appointments (Non-Ladder) - Dec 14, 2005, 2005 December (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - BPO Vote - Curriculum Issues - Dec 14, 2005, 2005 December (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Faculty Meetings, Agenda and Minutes, 1999 January - 2000 September (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Meetings, Agenda and Minutes, 2000 September - 2001 May (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Meetings, Agenda and Minutes, 2001 September - 2002 May (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Meetings, Agenda and Minutes, 2002 September - 2003 December (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Meeting - Jan 16, 2002, 2002 January (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Meeting - 2002 Feb 6, 2002, 2002 February (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Meeting - Feb 19, 2002, 2002 February (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Meeting - Feb 27, 2003, 2002 February (Box 18, Folder 8)